[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How heavy was the largest verified wild Komodo Dragon?", "correct_answer": "365 lbs.", "incorrect_answers": ["154 lbs.", "275 lbs.", "200 lbs."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Listening to what type of music is recommended for people who suffer from mood disorders?", "correct_answer": "Soft music", "incorrect_answers": ["Loud music", "Jazz", "Rock and roll"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the New Testament, which of the 12 Apostles gave Jesus a kiss, known as the kiss of betrayal?", "correct_answer": "Judas", "incorrect_answers": ["Thaddeus", "Bartholomew", "Simon the Zealot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Shelley Duvall won the Best Actress Award at the Cannes Festival, for her performance in what film, written and directed by Robert Altman?", "correct_answer": "3 Women", "incorrect_answers": ["Nashville", "Thieves Like Us", "McCabe  Mrs. Miller"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many of the AFI Top Ten American movies were created by foreign-born directors?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "7", "1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who said You got it in the movie The Goonies?", "correct_answer": "Andi", "incorrect_answers": ["Mikey", "Mouth", "Stef"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mesa Verde National Park in southern Colorado is best known for which of the following?", "correct_answer": "The best-preserved cliff dwellings in the U.S.", "incorrect_answers": ["Rather large, fossilized dinosaur tracks", "Massive trees known as Sequoias", "A very rare flower that only grows in the mountains"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "D-Day refers to one of the biggest military operations in history that took place on June 6, 1944. What was the pass word used by the Allied Forces on that day?", "correct_answer": "Mickey Mouse", "incorrect_answers": ["Overlord", "Sceptre", "Ike"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following starred in the movie Superfly?", "correct_answer": "Ron ONeal", "incorrect_answers": ["Louis Gossett", "Richard Roundtree", "Levar Burton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital and largest city of Romania?", "correct_answer": "Bucharest", "incorrect_answers": ["Ankara", "Sofia", "Kiev"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The mascot of which cereal is an animated sun, named Sunny?", "correct_answer": "Raisin Bran", "incorrect_answers": ["Special K", "None of these", "Total"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the collection of 100 novellas known as The Decameron?", "correct_answer": "Giovanni Boccaccio", "incorrect_answers": ["Emperor Huizong", "Eilhart von Oberge", "Alfonso VII of Le\u00f3n"]}]